Put an end to it.
Smoke him out and bring him here.
What about that thing?
It's safe.
However...
Your wife and daughter are riding on it as well.
What's a Rail Tracer?
The people will... disappear.
It will seem as if the train never existed in the first place.
All right, all right!
オ一ライ オ一ライ
お嬢様… あまり潮風に当たると
お体に障りますぞ
Miss, it's not good for your health to stand in the salty wind for so long.
すいません ベンヤ三ンさん… でも…
I'm sorry, Mr. Benjamin.
However...
もう少し もう少しだけ
ここで待っていたいんです
Just a little...
I want to wait here just a little longer.
Miss...
お嬢様…
ノイフ)
ダラス兄さん…
Dallas-niisan...
Welcome!
いらつしゃいませ!
I'm working at the English desk.
英語版のデスクを務めております
二コラスと申します
My name is Nicholas.
Well, well!
これはこれは
ルノラ一夕フアミ リ 一の
You gentlemen must be under the command of the Runorata family's Gustavo, yes?
グス夕一ヴオ氏 配下の方々ですね
なぜ分かつ た ?
How did you know?
それは私がデイリ一デイズ社の
社員だからです
That is because I am an employee of the Daily Days.
For an information shop like ours,
情報屋である私どもに
分からないことは まずございません
there is nothing we don't know about.
なら話は早い
Then we can cut to the chase.
ダラスジ工ノア一ドという
ガキを知ってるか?
Do you know of a kid called Dallas Genoard?
Yes! The second son of the famous Genoard family, Dallas Genoard is...
はい ダラスジ工ノア一ドは
名門ジ工ノア一ド家の次男で
現在行方不明とされる
札付きの不良少年…
a notorious juvenile delinquent whose whereabouts are currently unknown.
Tell us where he is!
看いつの行方を教えろ
とんな砦さ縄なことでもいい
Even the most trivial thing will do.
500ドル
500 dollars.
何?
What?
This information costs 500 dollars in cash.
この情報は現金で5叩 ドル
On top of that, I'd like to hear some information from you in return.
さらに あなた方から引き換えの
情報をーつ
情報だと ?
Information, you say?
Why the Runorata family is chasing Dallas Genoard.
なぜダラスジ工ノア一ドを
丿しノラ一夕'ファミリ一が追っているのか
I would like you to tell me the reason.
それを教えて頂きたい
教えてどうする
And what will you do with that information?
情報屋が情報を持たずして
どうなります?
What's an information shop without information?
もし俺たちが それを教えたとして
誰かがその情報を買いに来たら…
Suppose we tell you, and someone would come to buy that information...
Of course we would sell it to them!
もちろん売りますとも!
それが商売ですから !
It is our business after all.
You! If you had just listened quietly, you wouldn't have—
てめえ 黙つて聞いてりゃ
勝手なことを ! ほざっ
My apologies.
失礼
商売柄 色々 と物騒で してね
This business is quite dangerous, so...
Well now, why are you looking for Dallas Genoard?
さて… ダラスジ工ノア一ドを
捜す目的は?
Hey asshole!
てめえ!
You got a problem, brat?
文句あんのか ガキが
Get this? I'm part of the Runorata family.
いいか こちとらルノラ一夕
ファ三リ一の お世話になってんだ
I'm not someone you wannabe gangster punks can—
おめえらみてえなチンビラ風情が
盾つける…
どはつ
ぐはつ !
Runorata, you say?
丿しノラ一夕だ?
何偉そうに言つてんだ
What are you bragging about?!
You are like our servants!
てめえら うちの
使用人みてえなもんだろう力ヾ!
My old man is sucking up to my older bro,
親父や兄貴に取 り 入り や力ヾつて !
and now you're exploiting me?!
うちを食いもんにしやがつて !
The reason you guys get to eat at all is because of us!
てめえらが食つていけてんのは
うちのおかげだろうカヾ!
Stop it already.
もう およしなさい
死んでしまいますよ
He'll die.
何だ てめえは !
Who are you?
Leave!
行きなさい
ここは我々ガンド一ルのシマです
This is our, the Gandor's, turf!
丿しノラ一夕の名前はあまり
吹聴しないほうがよろしい
I'd rather not see the Runorata name mouthed around here.
はつ !
Gandor or whatever you may be, I don't know but...
ガンド一ルだか何だか知らねえが
余計なことしや力ヾつて!
butting into other people's business...
行くぞ !
Let's go.
誰だ あいつら ?
Who are they?
知らない人
Don't know 'em.
Well then, well then, well then!
さ一て さてさてえ
そろそろ始まるねぇ
俺たちのシヨ一カヾ!
It's about to start!
Our show, that is!
They're about to end, eh...
そろそろ終わつちまうねぇ
奴らの人生ヵヾ!
Their lives are!
うれしいねえ 楽しいねえ !
I'm so happy! It's so much fun!
I'm so excited that I can't sleep tonight!
俺 もう興奮して
今夜は眠れねえってよォ !
If you were looking forward to it so much,
そんなに楽しみなら
自分で行けばよかったのに
why didn't you go yourself?
だぁ一つてよお
しようがないじやん
But... I mean... It couldn't be helped, could it?
I lost at drawing straws...
くじ引きに
負けちまつたんだからよお !
ル一ア ! 俺は悔しい !
I'm so frustrated!
My dream is to...
俺の夢はよお 世の中の お前より
生きたがつてる奴をぜえんぶ殺して
kill everyone who wants to live more than you in the night,
and, in the end, I'm going to kill you thoroughly. Betting my life on it.
最後にお前を一生かけて たっぷり
殺し尽くしてやることなんだからよ
今 ここで殺してくれても
いいのよ… ラツ ド
I don't mind if you kill me here and now though, Ladd.
What are you saying?!
何言ってやがる!
ダメダメダメ !
No, no, no!
この世の中は まだまだまだ
This night is still overflowing with lots and lots and lots of people I have to kill!
殺してやらなきゃならねえ奴で
あふれ返つてるんだからな!
It'll be a long, long, long while before I get to killing you!
お前を殺してやるのは
まだまだまだ先だ!
ラツ ド...
Ladd...
So until then, don't die and stick with me.
だから それまで死なねえで
俺についてこい
いいな?
Okay?
Yes...
ビツキ一の奴
すつかり浮かれてるぜ
Vicky is in a perfectly good mood.
ああ クソ~
Ahh, shit...
Damn Vicky!
ビッキ一の奴 うらやましいな
マジでマジで!
I'm so jealous!
Seriously, seriously!
ああ イヤだ イヤだ
この世に神は もういねえ
I don't wanna!
God no longer exists in this world.
さっきビツキ一が
殺しちまったに違いねえ!
Vicky must have killed him just now!
だつたら見に行つたら
Why don't you go and see then?
それだ !
That's it!
You're right.
そうだよ 見に行きやいいじやん
I can just go and see.
バ力だなぁ 俺
I'm such an idiot.
こんなとこで
待っ乙る必要なかったんだよ
I don't have to wait here.
I just thought for a bit I had to wait here patiently.
ついつい ここで おとなしくしてなきゃ
いけねえと思つてたよ
I'll be back in a bit.
行つてくる !
おあっ !
Watch out, you—
気をつけろ このガキ… うつ
あ あああ ご ごめんなさい
すいません
I'm sorry!
I apologize.
The train's in terrible danger!
列車が大変なんです !
だ だから 僕 車掌室に
行かなくちゃいけなくて
That's why I have to go to the conductor's room.
と とにかく すいませんでした!
Anyway, I'm sorry!
あいつ
Him...
I'm sure he...
確か
It has become interesting.
面白くなつてきやがつた
Lua, can you go and check up on the conductor's room with him?
ルーア!
ちよつとよ そいつと一緒に
車掌室の檬子を
見てきてくれねえか?
~
そいで 顔に副童のあるカキかいたり
If there's a kid with a tattoo on his face, please grab him for now.
とりあえず取つ捕まえといてくれや
Okay.
何だよ この列車
随分おもしれえことになつてんなあ…
What's up with this train?
Things are surely getting interesting.
刺青のガキの言ってた
大変なことつてなあ
I wonder what on earth that terrible thing the tattoo'd kid spoke about could be.
一体なんだろうね?
It's getting dangerous...
やベえなあ オイ
そろそろ解放しねえと ぶつ壊れるな 俺
If I don't release myself soon, I'll explode!
Hey, stop it!
おい よせよ!
手が燃え尽きちまうぞ!
Your hand will burn to ashes!
It's okay!
平気だつて
See?
おお すげえな ランデイ
That's amazing, Randy!
It'll be great for our entertainment at tonight's party.
今夜のバ一テイ一の余興には
もってこいだ
Firo will most certainly be happy as well!
フイ一ロも きつと喜んでくれるぜ
おい ペツチヨ 何してる?
Hey.
Pezzo, what are you doing?
I'm gonna do it as well.
俺もやる
Hey, wait!
おい 待て お前の手袋は…
Your gloves are...
布製だろうが !
made of cloth, aren't they?!
おお~イ 熱いつて !
おい ! 消えねえじやねえか !
It's not going out!
It doesn't work if they aren't made of leather!
革じやねえとダメなんだ !
Take it off! Take your glove off!
落ち着け!
手袋を外せ! ほら とつとと !
熱! 熱!
平気か ヮ
You all right?
Yeah... I thought I was going to die.
ああ… 死ぬかと思つたぜ
てめえの巻き添えで
丸焼きはゴメンだぜ
I don't want to be burned alive together with you.
面目ねえ ハハハハハハハハ…
I'm so sorry.
Master Quates!
ク工一ツ様!
ついに完成しましたぞ !
It's finally finished!
あっ くつ うう
Damn!
クソ ! 何でこんな時に !
Why at a time like this?!
お嬢様 ここじゃけんベや
Miss, it is here!
あたすの幼なじみのいる
じようほうやつてのが
This is the information shop where my old friend works.
何です 新聞社ではございませんか
What is this? Isn't it a newspaper company?
ふむ これなら ある程度
信用できるかもしれませんぞ
We might be able to trust them to a certain extent.
ダラス坊ちゃまのことでも何でん聞けえ
分がるごっでぇ
Go ahead and ask them about Mr. Dallas... They'll know.
毎度ありい!
Come back again!
いらつしゃいませ
本巳は どのようなご用件で
Welcome!
How can we help you today?
3ゎぁ‥
Wow, amazing!
すげえなあ…
すごいつスね マイザ一さん
It sure is amazing, isn't it, Mr. Maiza?
For generations, the hats for executives in the Martillo family have been chosen here.
代々 マ丿しテイ一ジヨファミリ一の
幹部の帽子はここで選ばれているんです
I bought mine here as well.
私のも ここで買つ たんですよ
幹部かぁ… 実感逞かねえなぁ
Executive, eh?
I still haven't fully realized it...
実感なんてものは
なつてから湧くものです
Realizing is something you'll do once you've actually become it.
Is it really okay? With me?
ほんとにいいんでしようか 俺で
君だからいいんですよ フ イ一ロ
It's okay because it's you, Firo.
これ いいですよ マイザ一さん !
I like this one, Mr. Maiza!
俺にビツ夕リです !
It suits me perfectly.
ようこそ
マ丿しテイ一ジヨファ三ー」一へ...
Welcome to the Martillo family,
to the world of Camorra.
The Camorra is a mafia-like criminal organization, or secret society, in the region of Campania and the city of Naples in Italy.
力モ ツ ラの世界へ
Mr. Maiza, aren't you a day early?
マイザ一さん
ー日早いんじゃないですか?
儀式はもう始まっているんですよ
フイ一口
The ceremony has already started, Firo.
Oh, my apologies.
おっと失礼…
Hey, hey, watch where you walk.
おいおい 気をつけてくれよ
気をつけてくれよ
Watch where you walk.
Mr. Maiza, over there.
マイザ一さん あれ…
俺 ちよつと見てきます !
I'm going to take a quick look.
Firo, don't go berserk on me now.
フイ一ロ!
野次馬はおよしなさい!
心配なだけですよ
I'm just worried.
Are you all right?
大丈夫ですか ?
Ah, yes.
I'm very sorry.
申し訳あ り ませんでした
I'm looking for someone, so...
私 人を捜しているので これで…
おい あんた !
Hey!
You!
Wait up!
待てよ !
おっと
どうした ジヤグジ一
そんなに慌てて
What's the matter, Jacuzzi? Hurrying about like that.
大変なんだ この列車が
消えちゃうかもしれないんだ!
A disaster! This train might disappear!
だから 車掌さんの所に
行つてくるよ!
That's why I'm going to the conductor!
うあ?
あん?
あ ちようど良かつた
Just in time.
二一ス
姐さん
あね
Nice.
Sis.
ジヤグジ一は?
Where's Jacuzzi?
車掌んとこに行くつて 今さつき
He said he was going to the conductor's room just now...
ド二一は私と来て下さい
Please come with me, Donny.
As we take Jacuzzi back with us, we're going to check the luggage room.
ジヤグジ一を連れ戻すついでに
貨物室の様子を見てきます
I'm counting on you for the dining car, Nick.
二ツクは食堂車をお願いします
What do you mean, Nice-neesan...
何だい 二一ス姐さん
What do you want me to do with the dining car?
俺に食堂車をどうしろつてんだ
"I'm counting on you for the dining car, Nick."
二ツクは食堂車をお願いします
Ah, so she meant something like...
ああ つまり こういうことかな
"While we are working, please keep an eye on the people in the dining car."
二ツクは
私たちが仕事をしている間
食堂車の奴らを
見張つていて下さい!
ああ それは要するに
こういうことかな
So in other words... maybe something like this?
私たちが強盗している間
それを見つかつて 騒がれて
"If we are found while committing our robbery,"
"we can't allow them to make a ruckus and stop the train,"
列車を止められでもしたら
たまりません
だから二ック 食堂車の人たちを
おとなしくさせておいて
"so, Nick, keep the people in the dining car quiet."
Understood! Sis!
分かりやした 姐さん…
諸君…
Gentlemen!
これよりヒユ一イ師の
救出を開始する
We will begin our operation to save Sir Huey now.
おお… サマア一サ!
Samath!
Bruno!
工レア一ン!
久しい ! 久しいねえ 実に !
It's been a while! It sure has been a while!
ダラスジ工ノア一ド!
Dallas Genoard.
兄をご存じなんですね
You know my brother, right?
Who do you think I am?
僕を誰だと? ここをどこだと
思つていらつしゃる?
Where do you think this is?
ー年前から行方不明の
ジ工ノア一ド家の令息
The son of the Genoard family who disappeared a year ago,
the biggest juvenile delinquent of our age, Dallas Genoard!
だ力ヾ当代きつての不良少年
ダラスジ工ノア一ド!
強きにおもねり 弱きをいじめ
誰からも忌み嫌われた
Buried in aggressiveness, bullying the weak,
detested by everyone, a bastard of the worst kind!
最低のクズ野郎 !
兄は私には優しい人でした
My brother was a kind person to me.
悪L\! 悪かった!
少しロがすベっちまつた!
Excuse me, I apologize.
I went too far.
Pardon me, I'm sorry.
ごめんよ ! すまなかつたね…
君のお兄さんはきつと見つかる!
無事で見つかるから!
Your brother will definitely be found.
He'll be all right so, stop worrying. Okay?
だから安心して ! ね !
遅い ! 遅いよ !
Late! You're late!
お客様がお待ちかねだ !
待ちかねすきだよ!
Our client has been waiting!
Waiting too long!
どうもね !
Thanks.
Wait a bit.
ちよつと待つててね!
今 目を通すからね!
Let me read through it for a bit.
どうなんですか!?
How is it?
兄は ダラス兄さんは
どこにいるんですか!?
My brother... Where is my brother?
Tell me, please!
教えて下さい !
あ ああ そうだね…
Y-Yeah...
That's right.
ああ… 申し訳ない…
何も分からないんだよ
I'm so sorry...
We don't know anything.
我が社の情報網を持つ て しても
Even with the information our company has,
your brother's whereabouts remain a mystery.
まつたくの不明だそうだ…
ほんつとうに申し訳ない!
Completely unknown, it seems.
I am really truly sorry.
ぐはあ…
What, old man?
何だ ジジイ?
その箱はそんなに大切なもんか?
Is that box really so precious to you?
どれ こつちによこせよ~!
Let's see. Give it here.
Hold up.
く…
おっと…
うぐ
油断もスキもあったもんじやねえ
Can't give this guy any room!
しつつけえジジイだな
You're one stubborn bastard!
何見てんだ ガキ
What are you looking at, brat?!
いや… 強盗するなら
するなりの覚悟と技術力ヾあるのか
Oh no, I was just examining whether you guys were properly prepared,
見物させてもらつたのさ
and if you guys had the proper skills to execute a robbery.
うち
へツ… いいからガキは家に帰って
ママのオツパイでもしやぷつてな
Go home already and suck on your mom's tits or something.
そのガキの目から見ても
Even from the eyes of this brat,
お前らカヾやってるのは
ガキのお遊ぴにしか思えないぜ
what you are doing looks like nothing but child's play.
このクソガキが…
You shitty brat!
Looks like you want to get hurt, don't you?
よつぽど痛え目に遭いてえようだな
Rather than shitty brat, my name is Firo, but...
俺はクソガキじゃなくて
フイ一ロつて名前があるんだけど…
これでもマルテイ一ジヨファミリ一の
若衆なんだぜ
I'm still a young leader of the Martillo family.
それがどうした !
And how should that—
このガキ !
You brat!
おらあ!
へツ
You're bringing out knives in a fight like this?
おいおい…
こんなケン力に得物を出すのか?
うるせえ !
Shut up!
大丈夫か? 峯さん
Are you all right, old man?
Is it that precious to you?
そんなに大事なのか そいつは ?
Shut up! It has got nothing to do with the likes of you!
う うるさい!
お前のようなや葦すこは
関係ないものだ !
金カヾ目的なら くれてやる!
だから ささつとうせろ!
If you want money, I'll give it to you!
So leave now!
I just saved your life, you know?
俺はあんたの命の恩人だぜ
It's all right...
ま‥ L、L、や
なあ 爺さん
ーつ聞きたいんだけど…
Hey old man, I want to ask you something.
You haven't seen a woman wearing a light black suit around by any chance?
ここら辺で 黒の薄手のス一ツを
着た女を見なかつたか?
Hmm, no idea who you're talking about.
さ さあ… 知らんな
そうか
I see.
It's best if you leave while these guys are still out.
こいつらカヾ くたばつてる間に
とつとと行つたほうがいいぜ
See you!
じやあな
ハア… ハア… ハア… ハア…
ハァ… ハア… ハァ…
Firo...
フイ一ロ…
二ヒヒ 二ヒヒ…
I don't even have an appetite, Miria.
も う小腹もすかないぜ ミ ー丿 ア
A Japanese proverb used when someone cannot eat anymore of a certain dish, but for some reason still has room for dessert, hence the 'different stomach'.
The different stomach thing, right?
別腹つてやつだね
バアアン… ヒヒヒ
Well then, shall I get started?
さあ 始めますか
しやあ ! やるかあ !
Well then, let's do this!
All of you! Get down on the ground!
貴様ら全員 床に伏せろ !
Raise both hands. All of you!
てめえら全員 両手上げろ !
やいやいやい !
お前ら全員 動くなあっ !
Hey, hey, hey! All of you, don't move!
What do you want us...
ど どうしろと?
三リア
Miria.
What, Isaac?
なあに アイザツク?
Get down on the ground, raise both hands...
床に伏せて 両手を上げて
あと何だっけ?
What more was there?
"Don't move!" he said.
動くな ! だよ
Ahh, I see.
あ一 そうか!
え一と… お騒がせしました一
Uhmm, sorry for disturbing you.
You...
あんた
Mr. Barnes.
バ一ンズさん
It's here!
来たんだ… 遅かつたんだ…
We were too late!
It's already caught up!
もう追いついちゃったんだ
Rail Tracer!
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
Ladd Russo Enjoys
Talking A Lot and Slaughtering A lot
Hey Isaac, what does satsuriku (slaughter) mean?
The riku part must be the riku of tairiku (continent).
That's earth, right?
And satsu must be part of osatsu (banknotes).
That's money, right?!
In other words, it must mean a land made of banknotes!
That seems so much fun!
That really does seem fun!